Guide to the William R. Rambo Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Original Accession, 1939-1975
  - Academic Council, Undated
    - Budget projections, 1971-1975 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Constituency meetings, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Report on faculty self-discipline (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Miller Committee, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Academic Senate - Charter, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Academic Senate - SES discussions (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Academic Senate - American Assoc. Univ. Profs. statement: Govt. of Colleges & Univ. (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Academic Senate - Committee on Research Policy, classified research draft, 1967 Jul (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Academic Senate - ASSU (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - CAC [Coalition for an Academic Community] (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Science & Society Symposium (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Academic Senate - agendas, memoranda, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Academic Senate - agendas, memoranda, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - School of Engineering, 1964-1972
    See also box 13.
    - Misc. personnel correspondence, Undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Growth statistics, Undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Faculty meetings, 1964-1971 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - XC [Executive Committee], 1972 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Senior Research Associate, Undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - XC, 1970 Jul-Dec (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Conflict of interest, Undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - XC, 1971 Jan-Jul (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - XC, 1970 Jan-Jul (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Executive Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Engineering Senate, Prof Bryson's home, 1970 Sep 22 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Executive Committee Minutes, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Visiting Committee; Engineering, Undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Charts/statistics, misc., Undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - SES [Student Education Council], 1969 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Computer account, Undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Old "S" accounts, Undated (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Computer Corrsp., 1965-1967 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Advisory Council, 1967-1969 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - NSF Principal Investigators, Undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Student-Faculty Liason Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - "Import of Cutbacks Fed. Funding", Undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Replacement - Hybrid Computer, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Case study approach (NSF), Undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Goal of Engr. Education - reports, Undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Dept. of Mechanical Engr., Undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Chodorow - Applied Physics Div., Undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Operations Research Program, Undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Dept. of Civil Engr., Undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Center for Materials Research, Undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Engineering Economics, Undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Status of budget accounts, Undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Bio-Engineering/Bellville, Undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Proposal acceptance rates (KD), Undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Import cutbacks Fed. Fund., Undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Computer Committee, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Research support funds, Undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Research coord. (ROB), contracts, grants, Undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Interim reports sponsored research, Undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Honors Co-Op, memos & correspondence, Undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Stanford U. Honors Co-Op Progr., Undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Tau Beta Pi survey, Undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Fellowship awards, 1967-1969 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - GPA ranking of seniors, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - International Studies Program, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Summer research opportunities, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Misc., Undated (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - University, 1950-1975
    - Land & Building Development Comm., Undated (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Land & Building Dev. Comm. - Mins., 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Faculty Housing Sub Comm., 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Land & Bldg. Dev. Comm., 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Faculty Housing Sub Comm., 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Land & Bldg. Dev. Comm., 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Homeowners Association, 1966-1968 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Land & Bldg. Dev. (II), Planning Office Format, 1967 Dec 4 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Land & Bldg. Dev. Comm. - corresp., File I, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Land & Bldg. Dev. Comm., Minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Land & Bldg. Dev. Comm., Minutes, 1968-1969 Mar (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Land & Bldg. Dev. Comm. - corresp., file II, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - L & BD - Faculty-Staff Housing Sub., Undated (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Land & Bldg. Comm., correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Faculty Housing Sub Comm., 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Housing Sub Comm., 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Faculty Housing Sub Comm., 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Committee trips, etc., Undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Housing Sub Comm., 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Projected space needs, 1965-1975 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Comm. on Blgs. & Grounds (Bd. of Trustees Subcommittee), Undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Natural Disaster Sub-Committee, Undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Serra Street, Undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Freeway effects, Undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Proposal No. SE 1-65, Undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Outdoor Sculpture Subcomm., L & BD, Undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Land & Bldg. Dev. Comm. - miscell., Undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Advisory Comm. on Land & Bldg. Dev., Minutes, 1950-1952 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Space Engineering Bldg. Comm., undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Space Engineering Bldg., Corrsp., 1967 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - L & BD, Natural Disaster Subcomm., Undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Frenchman's Hill, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - L & BD Comm. Minutes, 1969 Apr-1970 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Personnel-research personnel titles, etc., Undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - IEEE Fellows[Institute of Electrical & Electronic Engineers, Inc.], Undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Stanford Associates - Annual Fund, Undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Stanford Associates - Annual Fund, Undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - NSF funding memos, Undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - National Science Foundation (NSF), Undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - NSF work papers, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - NSF, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - NSF, GFY 70, Undated (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - NSF (equipment), possible funds available, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - NSF - Research Initiation Grants, Undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - NSF (funding memo), 1967 Sep 22 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Cornell NSF, Undated (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - IEEE Fellows, 1968-1970 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - IEEE (misc.), undated (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - WESCON Conference, 1967 Aug (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Research Participation for College Teachers; Stanford for Engineering, new edition, Undated (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Academic Council, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Academic Council, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Academic Council Minutes, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Academic Council, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - ASEE [American Society for Engineering Education] and ECRC [Engineering College Research Council], 1964-1971
    - ASEE, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - ASEE, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - ASEE, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - ECRC Minutes, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - ASEE - Final Program, Diamond Jubilee meting, Undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - ASEE - travel forms, Undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - ECRC - Research Adm. Comm., 1964-1968 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - ECRC/ASEE, misc., Undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - ECRC Minutes, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - ASEE-ECRC faculty interest study, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - ECRC Minutes, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - ECRC Minutes, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - ECRC - general file, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - ECRC Membership Change Status & Rules - corrsp., Undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - ECRC - Wm. R. Rambo, Undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - ECRC, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Telecommunication Science Panel, 1966
    - Reports, summaries, etc., Undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - F. Committee structure & Charter, Undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - G. The Federal Communications Commission, Undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - H. Land Mobile - FAA - Radar - Law - Oceanography - USIA, Undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - I. Institute for Telecommunication Sciences and Aeronomy (ITSA), Undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - A. Antennas, Undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - B. Information - modulation, Undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - C. Propagation, Undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - D. Telecommunications, Undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - E. Satellite Communications Program, Undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Telecommunications file, Undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Commerce Dept. Panel - corresp., 1966 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - "A Report on Frequency Management ..." - draft, 1966 Jul 12 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - "Electromagnetic Spectrum Utilization..." - draft, 1966 Oct (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Communications Satellite Corp., AT&T, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Teaching Library, 1955-1969
    - EE 180b, Undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Notes, 1955-1964 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Problems, 1964-1965 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Files - storage, Undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Electronic Countermeasures, chapter: The Intercept Reciever, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Electronic & Radio Engineering - fifth edition, suggested format, 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - EE 159 3. grounded-grid power amplifer, Undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - EE 160 - general; "Supplemental Notes, 1962-63", 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - EE 160 - general; "Corrections ... Terman, 1958" (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - EE 160 -miscellaneous class notes, Undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - EE 160 - class C demonstration amplifier, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - EE 161: notes on modulation systems for class discussion, Undated (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - EE 159 2. Oscillations - - wanted & unwanted, Undated (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - EE 159 class tours, notes problems, Undated (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Eitel - McCullough class tours, Undated (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - EE 159 - general, Undated (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - EE 159 - student exam samples, 1964, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - EE 159 4. Terman 19-1,2; Qualitative ... Klystron Behavior, Undated (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - L.P. Brooks, Jr. - PhD application, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Problem solutions - Terman, Undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Problem solutions, Undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - EE 160 - examinations, Undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Roll Book, EE 160 (autumn quarter), EE 161 (winter quarter ), 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - EE 159 - class notes, problems (2 vol.), 1965-1966 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - EE 159 - class assignments, problems. Microwave & high power tubes (ECPD), 1966, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - EE 159 - 6. Terman 19-4, traveling-wave tube, Undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - EE 159 - 5. Terman 19-3, reflex Klystron, Undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - EE 213h, final, Undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - EE 213h - problems & solutions, 1967-1969 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - EE 180a - miscell. (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - University, personal & miscellaneous material, 1953-1971
    - Vandalism, Undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Proposal No. STL 8-68, Undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Memos, miscell., 1962-1971 (Box 13, Folder 14a)
    - Memos, miscell., 1962-1971 (Box 13, Folder 14b)
    - Personal correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - School of Engineering - Prof. Shockley/projects/plans, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Electrical Engineering Dep. faculty report, bio. material, Undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Campus recruiting, Undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Dr. Terman, Undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Travel corresp., 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - A.K. Subbotin - Russia, Undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - W.R. Rambo - McGraw Hill, Undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - W.R. Rambo - McGraw Hill, Undated (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Salaries, Undated (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - IEEE - International Convention Digest, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - O.G. Villard data, Undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - STL [Systems Techniques Lab] - misc. file, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - STL - Project Halloween, Undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - STL - activities/by date/talks & visits, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - STL - misc. file, Undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Security - Security Guide #100 & #241 (2 vol.), Undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Security - R.W. Lee, Undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Security - "Security Practices & Procedures" (2 vols.), 1969 Dec (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Security - budget, Research Security Adm., 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Security - correspondence, misc., 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Security - correspondence-misc., 1967 (Box 14, Folder 11a)
    - Security - correspondence-misc., 1967 (Box 14, Folder 11b)
    - Security - correspondence-misc., 1966 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Security - correspondence-misc., 1953-1965 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Security - report dissemination/contracts, Undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Security - receipts, Undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - ESTES - SES - Committee on Research Policy, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Research Policy Comm., Undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Hospital sit-in, 1971 Apr 9 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - ECRC Minutes, 1967 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Air Force Long-Range Planning Comm., Undated (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Denver Research Institute Research Program, Undated (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - IDA [Institute for Defense Analyses], Undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Socony-Mobile Oil Company, Inc. - grant, Undated (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Northrop Space Laboratories, Undated (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - ARPA - equipment grant negotiation, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Laser Antenna, Undated (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - ONR (59), Undated (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - ONR-64, Undated (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - AF 82, Undated (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - TASK 83, Undated (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - One-shot equipment, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Papers pub. by Siegman-Harris group, Undated (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - DA 394 - Kalman, Undated (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - N-0001, Undated (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - AF-0038, Undated (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - 0081, Undated (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - F-0110, Undated (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - N-0451, Undated (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - 0149, Undated (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - 1016, Undated (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - C-1245, Undated (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - C-1406, undated (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - C-1414, Undated (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - 1430, Undated (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - AF 1637, undated (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - C-1730, Undated (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - AF 3589, Undated (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Academic Council - memos & reports, 1966-1969 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - NASA - program, Undated (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - JSEP [Joint Services Electronic Program] and TAC [Technical Advisory Committee], 1963-1972
    - Joint Services contract discussion, inter-university "White Paper", 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Joint Services universities - miscell., 1968 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - JSEP Committee (TAC), 1967 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Technical reports (SU-SEL-70-044, 057, 058), 1970 Aug 7-9 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Stanford University Microwave Laboratory, Undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - JSEP principal investigators, Undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Brooklyn, Polytechnic Institute of, Undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - JSEP - replies, Undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Peter King, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - California, University of, Undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Research review, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - JSEP - University of Texas, Undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - JSEP - Harvard University, Undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - JSEP - Illinois, University of, Coordinated Science Laboratory, Undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - JSEP - MIT Research Laboratory of Electronics, Undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - TAC, Undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - TAC, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - TAC - meeting, 1965 Aug (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - TAC, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - TAC, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - TAC - meeting, 1969 Mar 21 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - TAC, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - TAC - meeting, 1967 Aug (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - TAC - meeting McC 240, 1971 Apr 8 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - TAC, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - JSEP - Monterey, Cal., 1971 Aug 10-11 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Universtiy, 1961-1972
    - Committee and Senate Handbook, preliminary edition, 1970 Jun (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Committee on Committees (incl. Minutes), 1969-1970
      - Correspondence, printed matter, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - #101-149, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - #150-199, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - #200-249, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - #250-299, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - #300-349, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - #350-399, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - #400-459, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - #450-499, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - #500-549, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - #550-559, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Inter-University Electronic Science Series, 1961-1963 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Korea - KAIS Contract, reports, 1969-1971 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Korea - KAIS correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - NASA (National Aeronautics & Space Administration), 1961-1970
      - General, 1961-1967, undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - "Instrumentation" program, Engineering, Medical School, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 17)
      - Proposal for Space Engineering Bldg. SE 2-65, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 18)
      - Study material, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - Study proposal, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 20)
      - Study questionnaire, 1964-1965 (Box 16, Folder 21)
      - Study report - WRR revisions, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Presidential Selection Committee, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - School of Engineering: Stanford Electronics Labs; consulting and research, 1949-1973
    - Applied Electronics Lab, 1954-1961
      - Building plans, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 24)
      - Building plans, 1956-1958 (Box 16, Folder 25)
      - Building plans, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 26)
      - Consulting arrangements, AEL personnel, 1956-1961 (Box 16, Folder 27)
      - Consulting - policy, 1955-1957 (Box 16, Folder 28)
      - Electronics Materials Committee, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 29)
      - Technical Program Committee, 1954-1955 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Air Force, 1954-1967
      - ARDC (Air Research & Dev. Command), 1956-1961 (Box 16, Folder 31)
      - CRC (Cambridge Research Center), 1954-1960 (Box 16, Folder 32)
      - Guidance Labs -proposal (Cannon), 1964-1965 (Box 16, Folder 33)
      - Guidance Labs - general (Cannon), 1964-1965 (Box 16, Folder 34)
      - Institute of Technology. Summer study program, 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 35)
      - Institute of Technology. AFSC-RTD E-W Career Dev. Program, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 36)
      - Miscellaneous dead, 1955-1959 (Box 16, Folder 37)
      - Miscellaneous, 1962-1967 (Box 16, Folder 38)
      - OSP (Office of Scientific Personnel), 1959-1961 (Box 16, Folder 39)
      - SAB (Scientific Advisory Board), 1959-1961 (Box 16, Folder 40)
      - SAB - general, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 41)
      - SAB - Reconnaissance Panel, 1960-1961 (Box 16, Folder 42)
      - SAB - Tactical Penetration Aids Ad Hoc Comm., 1963 (Box 16, Folder 43)
      - SAB - Tactical Penetration Aids draft report, Undated (Box 16, Folder 44)
      - SAB - Tactical Reconnaissance Panel, gen., 1964 (Box 16, Folder 45)
      - SAC (Strategic Air Command) - Presentation to Gen. LeMay "Research in ECM", 1955 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - SAC - dead, 1955-1959 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - SC (Systems Command) -RTD Avionics Lab review (Wright-Patterson), 1964 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - SC Project Forecast. General, 1962-1963 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - SC Project Forecast, ECM-ECCM draft panel report, Undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - WADC (Wright, Air Dev. Center), "Ferret Reconnaisance Consultation Group", 1958 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - WADC - miscellaneous, 1954-1961 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - AIL (Airborne Instruments Laboratory), 1951-1959 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Army, 1954-1972
      - Dead, 1959-1962 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - Electronics Advisory Group, 1968-1972 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - EIectronics Command, 1964-1967 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - General, 1964-1966 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Signal Corps, 1957-1961 (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - ARPA (Advanced Research Projects Agency), corresp., 1961-1967 (Box 17, Folder 14)
      - ARPA Industry-University Materials Program, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 15)
      - ARPA - Heckert, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 16)
      - ASEE (American Society for Engineering Education) - ECRC Conference on Administration of Interdisiplinary Research (Com. on Research Administration), 1963-1964 (Box 17, Folder 17)
      - ASEE-ECRC, miscell., 1964-1965 (Box 17, Folder 18)
      - ASEE-NSF Survey of' Grad. Ed. (Pettit, Gere), paper, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 19)
      - Balistic Missiles Division, 1959-1961 (Box 17, Folder 20)
      - Capehart-Farnsworh, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 21)
      - CGS Laboratories, Inc., 1958 (Box 17, Folder 22)
      - Contract info., general, 1954-1958 (Box 17, Folder 23)
      - Contract info. - project assignment, 1954-1955 (Box 17, Folder 24)
      - Convair, 1956-1958 (Box 17, Folder 25)
      - DDRE (Dir. of Defense Research & Engineering) - Advisory Group on Electronics Warfare, 1959-1971 (Box 17, Folder 26)
      - Defense Science Board, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 27)
      - Defense Science Board (EW), 1968 (Box 17, Folder 28)
      - ECM-RADC review, 1956 Jan (Box 17, Folder 29)
      - ECM trip to U.K., 1959 (Box 17, Folder 30)
      - ECRC ( Engineering College Research Council), Comm. on Research Administration, 1964-1965 (Box 17, Folder 31)
      - ECRC (research) Hoffman, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Electrical Engineering, Dept. of, 1949-1970
      - EE 180b - miscell., 1963-1965 (Box 17, Folder 33)
      - EE 180b Proc. IRE, The CAA VHF Omnirange, by Hurley, Anderson, Keary pp. 1506-1520, Undated (Box 17, Folder 34)
      - EE 180b Proc. IRE, Standards on Radio Aids to Navigation: Definition of Terms, pp.1364-1371, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 35)
      - EE - E.C.P.D. (Engineers' Council for Professional Development), 1958-1959 (Box 17, Folder 36)
      - EE - Energy Conversion and Control (Subcommittee of Ph.D. Examination Committee), 1957-1958 (Box 17, Folder 37)
      - Ph.D. examinations, exam questions, 1958-1959 (Box 17, Folder 38)
      - Committees - Exec. Com., 1960-1962 (Box 17, Folder 39)
        Includes Minutes.
      - Executive Comm., 1962-1964 (Box 17, Folder 40)
      - Executive Comm., 1970 Jul 31 (Box 17, Folder 41)
      - E.E. 160 - miscell., 1956-1964 (Box 17, Folder 42)
      - Long-Range Planning Committee, 1958-1963 (Box 17, Folder 43)
      - May-Weaver, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 44)
      - Electronic and Radio Engineering - fourth ed. Contributor, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 45)
        Includes photographs.
      - Employment, AEL-student program, 1955-1958 (Box 17, Folder 46)
      - Engineering, School of - problems of underdev. nations, 1962-1964 (Box 17, Folder 47)
      - ESL (Evans Signal Laboratory) - contract proposals, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 48)
      - EWAG (Electromagnetic Warfare Advisory Group) of ARDC, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 49)
      - Figures - extra copies, Undated (Box 17, Folder 50)
      - Gallagher, Dr. Philip, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 51)